Guide to the University Faculty records, 1909-1998.
University Faculty records, 1909-1998
Division of Rare and Manuscript Collections, Cornell University Library
University Faculty records, 1909-1998.
11-2-707
Cornell University. University Faculty.
42.8 cubic ft.
Correspondence, Printed Materials.
Division of Rare and Manuscript Collections, Cornell University Library
Minutes, notes, agendas, correspondence, and other printed material of the Cornell University Faculty.
COLLECTION DESCRIPTION
Minutes, notes, agendas, correspondence, and other printed material of the Cornell University Faculty.
SUBJECTS
Names:
Cornell University.; Cornell University--Faculty.
INFORMATION FOR USERS
Access Restrictions:
#11-1-375, 11-1-895, 11-1-1175, 11-1-1272, 11-1-1371, 11-1-1415, 11-1-1547, 11-1-1616, and 11-5-1740 are restricted to the permission of the office of origin except for Boxes 1-26 of #11-1-895.
RELATED MATERIALS
Includes collections #11-1-895, 11-1-375, 11-1-1175, 11-1-1415, 11-1-1371, 11-1-1272, 11-1-1547, 11-1-1616, 11-2-926, and 11-5-1740.
CONTAINER LIST
- Series I. Dean of the Faculty Records (11-1)
  - Collection 11-1-375 (Box 1-32)
    - 1909-1910 (Box 1)
    - 1911 (Box 2)
    - 1912 (Box 3)
    - 1913 (Box 4)
    - 1914 (Box 5)
    - 1915 (Box 6)
    - 1916 (Box 7)
    - 1917 (Box 8)
    - 1918 (Box 9)
    - 1919 (Box 10)
    - Jan.-Apr. 1920 (Box 11)
    - May-Dec. 1920 (Box 12)
    - Jan.-July 1921 (Box 13)
    - Aug.-Dec. 1921 (Box 14)
    - Jan.-May 1922 (Box 15)
    - June-Dec. 1922 (Box 16)
    - Jan.-May 1923 (Box 17)
    - June-Dec. 1923 (Box 18)
    - Jan.-Mar. 1924 (Box 19)
    - Apr.-Dec. 1924 (Box 20)
    - 1925 (Box 21)
    - Jan.-Apr. 1926 (Box 22)
    - May-Dec. 1926 (Box 23)
    - Jan.-May 1927 (Box 24)
    - June-Dec. 1927 (Box 25)
    - Jan.-June1928 (Box 26)
    - July 1928 - Mar. 1929 (Box 27)
    - Apr.-Dec. 1929 (Box 28)
    - 1930-31 (Box 29)
    - 1932-35 (Box 30)
    - Undated (Box 31)
    - Undated (Box 32)
  - Collection 11-1-895 (Box 1-29)
    - Faculty Meetings, 1956-1957 (Box 1, Folder 1)
    - University Faculty Meeting Work Sheets, 1956-1957 (Box 1, Folder 2)
    - University Faculty Meeting Work Sheets, 1957-1958 (Box 1, Folder 3)
    - University Faculty Meetings, 1957-1958 (Box 1, Folder 4)
    - University Faculty Meetings, 1958-1959 (Box 1, Folder 5)
    - University Faculty Meetings, 1958-1959 (Box 1, Folder 6)
    - Faculty Meeting, October 1959 (Box 1, Folder 7)
    - Faculty Meeting, November 1959 (Box 1, Folder 8)
    - Faculty Meeting, December 1959 (Box 1, Folder 9)
    - Faculty Meeting, January 1960 (Box 1, Folder 10)
    - Faculty Meeting, February 1960 (Box 1, Folder 11)
    - Faculty Meeting, March 1960 (Box 1, Folder 12)
    - Faculty Meeting, April 1960 (Box 1, Folder 13)
    - Faculty Meeting, May 1960 (Box 1, Folder 14)
    - Special Meeting of University Faculty, May 25, 1960 (Box 1, Folder 15)
    - Faculty Meeting, October 1960 (Box 1, Folder 16)
    - Faculty Meeting, November 1960 (Box 1, Folder 17)
    - Faculty Meeting, December 1960 (Box 1, Folder 18)
    - Faculty Meeting, January 1961 (Box 1, Folder 19)
    - Faculty Meeting, February 1961 (Box 1, Folder 20)
    - Faculty Meeting, March 8, 1961 (Box 1, Folder 21)
    - Faculty Meeting, April 1961 (Box 1, Folder 22)
    - Faculty Meeting, May 1961 (Box 1, Folder 23)
    - Faculty Meeting, October 11, 1961 (Box 1, Folder 24)
    - Faculty Meeting, November 1961 (Box 1, Folder 25)
    - Special Meeting of University Faculty, November 10, 1961 (Box 1, Folder 26)
    - Faculty Meeting, December 1961 (Box 1, Folder 27)
    - Faculty Meeting, January 1962 (Box 1, Folder 28)
    - Faculty Meeting, February 1962 (Box 1, Folder 29)
    - Faculty Meeting, March 1962 (Box 1, Folder 30)
    - Faculty Meeting, April 11, 1962 (Box 1, Folder 31)
    - Faculty Meeting, May 9, 1962 (Box 1, Folder 32)
    - Faculty Meeting, October 17, 1962 (Box 1, Folder 33)
    - Faculty Meeting, November 14, 1962 (Box 1, Folder 34)
    - Faculty Meeting, December 12, 1962 (Box 1, Folder 35)
    - Faculty Meeting, January 16, 1963 (Box 1, Folder 36)
    - Faculty Meeting, February 1963 (Box 1, Folder 37)
    - Faculty Meeting, March 13, 1963 (Box 1, Folder 38)
    - Faculty Meeting, April 10, 1963 (Box 1, Folder 39)
    - Faculty Meeting, May 8, 1963 (Box 1, Folder 40)
    - Special Faculty Meeting, September 25, 1963 (Box 1, Folder 41)
    - Faculty Meeting, October 9, 1963 (Box 1, Folder 42)
    - Faculty Meeting, November 13, 1963 (Box 1, Folder 43)
    - Special Faculty Meeting, December 4, 1963 (Box 1, Folder 44)
    - Faculty Meeting, December 11 (Box 1, Folder 45)
    - Faculty Meeting, January 13 (Box 1, Folder 46)
    - Faculty Meeting, February 12 (Box 1, Folder 47)
    - Faculty Meeting, March 11 (Box 1, Folder 48)
    - Faculty Meeting, April 5 (Box 1, Folder 49)
    - Faculty Meeting, May 27 (Box 1, Folder 50)
    - Lectures on Nuclear Peril, Account 691 (Box 2, Folder 1)
    - Expenditures, Account 178, 1961-1962 (Box 2, Folder 2)
    - Dean of Faculty, Day Hall, Equipment, No. 188 (Box 2, Folder 3)
    - Account 178, Faculty Handbooks (Box 2, Folder 4)
    - Hourly Wages, Account 52 - Closed Out (Box 2, Folder 5)
    - Special Equipment Account (Box 2, Folder 6)
    - General Expense Account No. 178, 1963-1964 (Box 2, Folder 7)
    - Dean of the Faculty Account No. 178, 1962-1963 (Box 2, Folder 8)
    - Budget, 1946-1962 (Box 2, Folder 9)
    - Prize Awards, Spring 1962 (Box 2, Folder 10)
    - Prize Competitions, Announcement, 1962-1964 (Box 2, Folder 11)
    - Prize Committee Replacements, 1962-1963 (Box 2, Folder 12)
    - Annual Report to the President, 1955-1956 (Box 2, Folder 13)
    - Annual Report to the President, 1956-1957 (Box 2, Folder 14)
    - Annual Report to the President, 1957-1958 (Box 2, Folder 15)
    - Annual Report to the President, 1958-1959 (Box 2, Folder 16)
    - Annual Report to the President, 1959-1960 (Box 2, Folder 17)
    - Annual Report to the President, 1960-1961 (Box 2, Folder 18)
    - Annual Report to the President, 1961-1962 (Box 2, Folder 19)
    - Annual Report to the President, 1962-1963 (Box 2, Folder 20)
    - Centennial (Adult Education) (Box 2, Folder 21)
    - Graduate School of Nutrition, Social Science Sub-Committee (Home Economics) (Box 2, Folder 22)
    - Academic Freedom and Tenure Committee (Box 3, Folder 1)
    - No. 1, 1953-1956 (Folder 3, Folder 2)
    - Academic Freedom and Tenure, Committee on (Correspondence on Sub-Committee on Academic Problems arising from Governmental Investigations) (Box 3, Folder 3)
    - Academic Freedom Reports and Tenure (Box 3, Folder 4)
    - Communism - Pleading Fifth Amendment (Correspondence on Sub-Committee on Academic Problems arising from Governmental Investigations) (Box 3, Folder 5)
    - Alvin W. Hoffer (Geneva) (Academic Freedom and Tenure) (Box 3, Folder 6)
    - Academic Freedom and Tenure (Lewis L. Ageroni) (Box 3, Folder 7)
    - Finlay Case, Academic Freedom and Tenure, 1953 (Box 3, Folder 8)
    - Academic Freedom and Tenure, Committee on (2) (Box 3, Folder 9)
    - Academic Freedom and Tenure, Committee on (3), 1957-1958 (Box 3, Folder 10)
    - Academic Freedom and Tenure, Committee on (4), 1959-1960 (Box 3, Folder 11)
    - Academic Freedom and Tenure #5, 1960 (Box 3, Folder 12)
    - Academic Freedom and Tenure, 1960-1961 (Box 3, Folder 13)
    - Academic Freedom and Tenure, 1961-1962 (Box 3, Folder 14)
    - Special Correspondence on Audio and Visual Aids (Box 3, Folder 15)
    - Cabinet (Box 3, Folder 16)
    - Calendar, Committee on (Box 3, Folder 17)
    - Policy Planning Committee (4) (Box 3, Folder 18)
    - C.U.R.W. (Box 3, Folder 19)
    - Commencement, Committee on (Box 3, Folder 20)
    - Cooperative Purchasing, Committee on (Box 3, Folder 21)
    - Cornell University, Miscellaneous Requests for Information about things at (Box 3, Folder 22)
    - 1941-1954 (Box 3, Folder 23)
    - Economic Status of the Faculty Committee (Retirement Fund and Systems, Credit Union, Rceive File Retirement Age Mandatory) (Box 4, Folder 1)
    - Committee on Economic Status of the Faculty (Retirement Funds and Systems, Credit Union, Emergency File Retirement Age Mandatory) (Box 4, Folder 2)
    - Economic Status of the Faculty, 1960 (Box 4, Folder 3)
    - Economic Status of the Faculty, 1959 (Box 4, Folder 4)
    - Economic Status of the Faculty, 1958 (Box 4, Folder 5)
    - Committee on Economic Status of the Faculty, 1957-1958 (Box 4, Folder 6)
    - Committee on Elections (Box 4, Folder 7)
    - Committee on Economic Status of the Faculty (Box 4, Folder 8)
    - Economic Status of the Faculty (Box 4, Folder 9)
    - Analysis of Cornell University Faculty (Box 4, Folder 10)
    - Salaries, 1957 (Box 4, Folder 11)
    - Committee on Economy (Box 4, Folder 12)
    - The Evaluation and Improvement of Instruction, Committee on (Box 4, Folder 13)
    - Extramural Courses, Advisory Committee for (Box 4, Folder 14)
    - Faculty Council, 1961 (Box 4, Folder 15)
    - Faculty Council, 1960 (Box 4, Folder 16)
    - Faculty Council, 1959 (Box 4, Folder 17)
    - Faculty Council, 1958 (Box 4, Folder 18)
    - Faculty Council, 1957 (Box 4, Folder 19)
    - University Policy, Committee on (Minutes), 1949-1950 (Box 4, Folder 20)
    - University Policy, Committee on (Minutes, etc.), 1956-1957 (Box 4, Folder 21)
    - Committee on University Policy (Minutes), 1945-1946 (Box 4, Folder 22)
    - Minutes of Committee on University Policy, October 1946 - June 1949 (Box 4, Folder 23)
    - Faculty Research Grants, Committee on (Box 4, Folder 24)
    - Special Committee on the Exchange of Faculty Children between Cornell and other colleges and universities (Box 4, Folder 25)
    - Governmental Investigations Committee (Sub-committee of the University Policy Committee) (Box 4, Folder 26)
    - Committee on Inter-College Transfers (Box 4, Folder 27)
    - Inter-Faculty Relations, Committee on, 1950-1957 (Box 4, Folder 28)
    - Inter-Faculty Relations, University Faculties Committee on (to compile list of courses open to all undergrads (Box 4, Folder 29)
    - Committee on Long-Range Planning (Box 5, Folder 1)
    - Long-Range Planning, Committee on, #1, 1957-1958 (Box 5, Folder 2)
    - Long-Range Planning, Committee on, #2, 1958 (Box 5, Folder 3)
    - Long-Range Planning, Committee on, #3 (Box 5, Folder 4)
    - Long-Range Planning, Committee on, #4 (Box 5, Folder 5)
    - Long-Range Planning, Committee on, #5 (Box 5, Folder 6)
    - Long-Range Planning, Committee on, #6 (Box 5, Folder 7)
    - Long-Range Planning, Committee on, #7 (Box 5, Folder 8)
    - Long-Range Planning, Committee on, #8 (Box 5, Folder 9)
    - Long-Range Planning, Committee on, #9 (Box 5, Folder 10)
    - Long-Range Planning, Committee on, #10 (Box 5, Folder 11)
    - Long-Range Planning, Committee on, #11 (Box 5, Folder 12)
    - Long-Range Planning, Committee on, #12 (Box 5, Folder 13)
    - Lectures, Committee on University, 1958-1960, July (Box 5, Folder 14)
    - Lectures, Committee on University (Box 5, Folder 15)
    - Malti Case, Men's Judiciary Board, Proposed Dorm Judiciary Board (Box 6, Folder 1)
    - Committee on Military Curricula, #3, May 1960 (Box 6, Folder 2)
    - Committee on Military Curricula, #2, March 1960 - April 1960 (Box 6, Folder 3)
    - Committee on Military Curricula, #1, October 1959 - February 1960 (Box 6, Folder 4)
    - Military Curricula, Committee on, 1958 - September 1959 (Box 6, Folder 5)
    - Military Curricula, Committe on (Box 6, Folder 6)
    - Military Service, Committe on (Box 6, Folder 7)
    - Music, Committee on, 1953-1957 (Box 6, Folder 8)
    - Stanley Committee on Military Curricula (Box 6, Folder 9)
    - Necrology, 1963-1964 (Box 6, Folder 10)
    - Necrology, 1962-1963 (Box 6, Folder 11)
    - Natural Areas Committee (Box 6, Folder 12)
    - Committee on Nominations, 1958-1959 (Box 6, Folder 13)
    - Committee on Nominations, 1955-1957 (Box 6, Folder 14)
    - Committee on Nominations, 1953-1954 (Box 6, Folder 15)
    - Orientation Advisory Board (Box 6, Folder 16)
    - Prizes and Prize Contests (Box 6, Folder 17)
    - Committee on Prizes (Box 6, Folder 18)
    - The Samson Fine Arts Prize (Box 6, Folder 19)
    - Prizes and Prize Contests, General (Box 6, Folder 20)
    - Alumni Prize for Scholarship - Agriculture (Box 6, Folder 21)
    - American Institute of Architects - Student Medal (Box 6, Folder 22)
    - The Baird Prizes - Architecture (Box 6, Folder 23)
    - The Barnes Shakespeare Prize (Box 6, Folder 24)
    - The Frank A. Barton Prize (Box 6, Folder 25)
    - James Gordon Bennett Prize - Vet. (Box 6, Folder 26)
    - The Ann Bessie Prize - Vet (Box 6, Folder 27)
    - The Charles Gross Bondy Prizes - Vet (Box 6, Folder 28)
    - The Clifton Beckwith Brown Memorial Medal - Architecture (Box 6, Folder 29)
    - The George Chapman Cauldwell Prize - Chemistry (Box 6, Folder 30)
    - The W.D.P. Carey Exhibition - Law (Box 6, Folder 31)
    - Henry Chalmers Prize - Endowment (Box 6, Folder 32)
    - Corson-Browning Prize (Box 6, Folder 33)
    - The Corson French Prize (Box 6, Folder 34)
    - The Bess Burlow Cohen Prize (Box 6, Folder 35)
    - The Juliette MoMannes Currant Prize (Box 6, Folder 36)
    - The Charles Lee Crandell Prizes - Engineering (Box 6, Folder 37)
    - The Paul Dickinson Prize - Architecture (Box 6, Folder 38)
    - The Eastman Prize for Public Speaking - Agriculture (Box 6, Folder 39)
    - The '86 Memorial Prize (Box 6, Folder 40)
    - The Farm Life Challenge Prizes - Agriculture (Box 6, Folder 41)
    - The Forbes-Hermann Prizes in Playwriting (Box 6, Folder 42)
    - The Fuertes Medals (Box 6, Folder 43)
    - The Fuertes Memorial Prizes in Playwriting (Box 6, Folder 44)
    - The Goth Prize - German (Box 6, Folder 45)
    - The Graduate Prize in Philosophy (Box 6, Folder 46)
    - The Gilford Essay Prize (Box 6, Folder 47)
    - Ideler, John and Louise, Endowment (Box 6, Folder 48)
    - Manuscript Club Short Story (Box 6, Folder 49)
    - Special 1946 Hermann Prize in New York State Thesis (Box 6, Folder 50)
    - The Harold Adler Lovinburg Prize - Chemistry (Box 6, Folder 51)
    - The Addison D. Merry Memorial Prize - Vet (Box 6, Folder 52)
    - The Lunar L. Hessenger Memorial Prize (Box 6, Folder 53)
    - Michael Mitchell - Prize Endowment (Box 6, Folder 54)
    - The Alfred Moritz Michael Memorial Prize - Medical (Box 6, Folder 55)
    - The Jane Miller Prizes - Vet (Box 6, Folder 56)
    - The Morrison Poetry Prize (Box 6, Folder 57)
    - Neurology Prize for Efficiency in Medical (Box 6, Folder 58)
    - '94 Memorial Prize (Box 6, Folder 59)
    - Charles Lathrop Pack Foundation Forestry Prize - Agriculture (Box 6, Folder 60)
    - The John Metcalf Polk Memorial Prizes - Medical (Box 6, Folder 61)
    - William M. Polk Memorial Prizes - Medical (Box 6, Folder 62)
    - The Rice Debate Stage - Agriculture (Box 6, Folder 63)
    - The Ring Memorial Prizes - Agriculture (Box 6, Folder 64)
    - The Charles Goodwin Sands Memorial Medals - Architecture (Box 6, Folder 65)
    - The Gustaf Segalman Prizes in Obstetrics - Medical (Box 6, Folder 66)
    - The Sherman Bennett Prize (Box 6, Folder 67)
    - The Sibley Prizes - Engineering (Box 6, Folder 68)
    - The Robert Harris Simpson Memorial Prize - Engineering (Box 6, Folder 69)
    - The Stuart Prize - Agriculture (Box 6, Folder 70)
    - William W. Stout Scholarship Endowment (Box 6, Folder 71)
    - The Harace K. White Prizes - Vet. (Box 6, Folder 72)
    - The J.G. White Prizes in Spanish and English (Box 6, Folder 73)
    - The Whiting Prize in Otology - Medical (Box 6, Folder 74)
    - The Moses Coit Tyler Prizes (Box 6, Folder 75)
    - The Martin Wright Sampson Memorial Prize (Box 6, Folder 76)
    - Edward Palmer York Memorial Prize - Architecture (Box 6, Folder 77)
    - The Whitford Prize (Box 6, Folder 78)
    - Central New York Architects Prize (Box 6, Folder 79)
    - Mary Louise Prize - Veterinary (Box 6, Folder 80)
    - Plenary Committee (Box 7, Folder 1)
    - Prizes, Committee on, 1957-1958 (Box 7, Folder 2)
    - Prizes, Commitee on, 1955-1957 (Box 7, Folder 3)
    - Special Committee on Pre-Registration Prizes, Manuscripts, etc., 1958 (Box 7, Folder 4)
    - Publications and Printing, Committee on (Box 7, Folder 5)
    - Committee to consider Problems re: Radio, TV, Photo Science, Audio-Visual Aids (Box 7, Folder 6)
    - Registration and Schedules, Committee on, 1958-1959 (Box 7, Folder 7)
    - Registration and Schedules, Committee on, 1952-1957 (Box 7, Folder 8)
    - Requirements for Graduation, Committee on, September 1956-1957 (Box 7, Folder 9)
    - Requirements for Graduation, Committee on, (Minutes) Legislation and Policy Statement attached to Minutes, January 1952 (Box 7, Folder 10)
    - Requirements for Graduation, Committee on, (Military, P.T. and Residence), 1949-1958 (Box 7, Folder 11)
    - Requirements for Graduation, Letters re: actions taken, conscientious objectors, etc. (Box 7, Folder 12)
    - Confidential Records (F.B.I.) (Box 7, Folder 13)
    - Scheduling of Public Events, Committee on, June 1959-1961 (Box 7, Folder 14)
    - Scheduling of Public Events, Committee on, 1957-1960 (Box 7, Folder 15)
    - Scheduling of Public Evets, Committee on, 1952-1956 (Box 7, Folder 16)
    - Senior, John L., Professorship in American Civilization (Box 7, Folder 17)
    - Student Council Activities Board (Box 7, Folder 18)
    - Minutes of the Committee on Long Range Planning, October 1959-1963 (Box 7, Folder 19)
    - Minutes of the Committee on Long Range Planning, May 1957 - June 1959 (Box 7, Folder 20)
    - Faculty Council, Ad Hoc Committee on Student Affairs, 1958 (Box 8, Folder 1)
    - Student Affairs, Committee on, #1 (Box 8, Folder 2)
    - Student Conduct, Committee on, June 1952-1958 (Box 8, Folder 3)
    - Student Activities, Committee on (Box 8, Folder 4)
    - Student Activities, Committee on (Minutes) (Box 8, Folder 5)
    - Committee on Student Housing (Box 8, Folder 6)
    - Tenure and Efficiency Committee (Possibility for Research Associates, Technicians, etc.) (Box 8, Folder 7)
    - Undergraduate Committee on Secondary Schools (Box 8, Folder 8)
    - University Broadcasting, Committee on (Box 8, Folder 9)
    - University Policy, Committee on (Miscellaneous) (Box 8, Folder 10)
    - University testing and service bureau, Administrative Board (Box 8, Folder 11)
    - War Alumni Certificate (Box 8, Folder 12)
    - Compulsory Military Drill (Box 8, Folder 13)
    - Centennial Planning #1 (Box 9, Folder 1)
    - Centennial Planning #2 (Box 9, Folder 2)
    - Centennial Planning #3 (Box 9, Folder 3)
    - Centennial Planning (Position Papers, Originals and Correspondence) (Box 9, Folder 4)
    - Positions Papers (Box 9, Folder 5)
    - C.A. Hanson Copies sent to Faculty Council (Box 9, Folder 6)
    - Plan for Student Housing, Cornell University (Box 9, Folder 7)
    - Long-range planning (Box 9, Folder 8)
    - L.R.P. and Academic Deans (Box 9, Folder 9)
    - Preliminary Statement, Cornell University Centennial Campaign, November 15, 1961 (Box 9, Folder 10)
    - Preliminary Statement, Confidential Assessment of Cornell's Immediate Needs and Opportunities for its Centennial Program, September 30, 1961 (Box 9, Folder 11)
    - Centennial (for Dean of Faculty) (Box 9, Folder 12)
    - Long-range planning sub-committee on international affairs (Box 9, Folder 13)
    - L.R.P. (cont'd) (Box 9, Folder 14)
    - Nuclear Peril Materials (Speeches, etc.) (Box 9, Folder 15)
    - The Size of the University (Box 9, Folder 16)
    - Academic Freedom and Responsibility, 1974-1975 (Box 27, Folder 1)
    - Academic Programs and Policies, 1974-1975 (Box 27, Folder 2)
    - Academic Records and Instruction, 1974-1975 (Box 27, Folder 3)
    - Budget, 1974-1975 (Box 27, Folder 4)
    - Executive Committee, 1974-1975 (Box 27, Folder 5)
    - Freedom of Teaching and Learning, 1974-1975 (Box 27, Folder 6)
    - International Student Affairs, 1974-1975 (Box 27, Folder 7)
    - Lectures, 1974-1975 (Box 27, Folder 8)
    - Library Board, 1973-1974, 1974-1975 (Box 27, Folder 9)
    - Subcommittee of the Library Board, 1974-1975 (Box 27, Folder 10)
    - Membership of the University Faculty, 1973-1974 (Box 27, Folder 11)
    - Music, 1974-1975 (Box 27, Folder 12)
    - Nominations and Elections, 1974-1975 (Box 27, Folder 13)
    - Personnel Policy & Planning Board, 1974-1975 (Box 27, Folder 14)
    - Physical Education, 1974-1975 (Box 27, Folder 15)
    - Professional & Economic Status, 1974-1975 (Box 27, Folder 16)
    - Research Policies, 1974-1975 (Box 27, Folder 17)
    - Review and Procedures, 1974-1975 (Box 27, Folder 18)
    - University - ROTC REelationships, 1974-1975 (Box 27, Folder 19)
    - Budget, 1975-1976 (Box 28, Folder 1)
    - Budget, 1974-1975 (Box 28, Folder 2)
    - Faculty and FCR Meetings, 1975-1976 (Box 28, Folder 3)
    - Faculty and FCR Meetings, 1974-1975 (Box 28, Folder 4)
    - Faculty and FCR Meetings, 1973-1974 (Box 28, Folder 5)
    - Memorial Statements of the Faculty, 1975-1976 (Box 28, Folder 6)
    - Academic Freedom and Responsibility Committee, 1975-1976, 1976-1977 (Box 29, Folder 1)
    - Academic Programs and Policies Committee, 1975-1976, 1976-1977 (Box 29, Folder 2)
    - Academic Records and Instruction Committee, 1975-1976, 1976-1977 (Box 29, Folder 3)
    - Budget, 1976-1977 (Box 29, Folder 4)
    - Budget Committee, 1975-1976, 1976-1977 (Box 29, Folder 5)
    - Committees, ad hoc: Bill of Rights; Environmental Studies; Faculty Counselors, President's Assistants on the Budget; Self-Governance, Presidential Commission on, 1971-1976 (Box 29, Folder 6)
    - Executive Committee, 1975-1976, 1976-1977 (Box 29, Folder 7)
    - FCR and Faculty Meetings, 1976-1977 (Box 29, Folder 8)
    - Freedom of Teaching and Learning Committee, 1975-1976, 1976-1977 (Box 29, Folder 9)
    - International Student Affairs Committee, 1975-1976, 1976-1977 (Box 29, Folder 10)
    - Lectures Committee, 1975-1976, 1976-1977 (Box 29, Folder 11)
    - Music Committee, 1975-1976, 1976-1977 (Box 29, Folder 12)
    - Nominations and Elections Committee, 1975-1976, 1976-1977 (Box 29, Folder 13)
    - Personnel Planning and Policy Board, 1975-1976, 1976-1977 (Box 29, Folder 14)
    - Physical Education Committee, 1975-1976, 1976-1977 (Box 29, Folder 15)
    - Professional and Economic Status Committee, 1975-1976, 1976-1977 (Box 29, Folder 16)
    - Recombinant DNA Committee, 1976-1977 (Box 29, Folder 17)
    - Research Policies Committee, 1975-1976, 1976-1977 (Box 29, Folder 18)
    - Review and Procedures Committee, 1975-1976, 1976-1977 (Box 29, Folder 19)
    - University - ROTC Relationships Committee, 1975-1976, 1976-1977 (Box 29, Folder 20)
  - Collection 11-1-1175 (Box 1-7)
    - Academic Freedom and Tenure, 1962-1966 (Box 1, Folder 1)
    - Academic Integrity, 1962-1966 (Box 1, Folder 2)
    - Festival of Contemporary Arts, 1963-1965 (Box 1, Folder 3)
    - Arts, President's Comm. on, 1964-1965 (Box 1, Folder 4)
    - Arts, Committee on, 1964-1966 (Box 1, Folder 5)
    - Budget - Codification of Legislation, 1959-1964 (Box 1, Folder 6)
    - Budget - Quality of Undergraduate Education, 1965-1966 (Box 1, Folder 7)
    - Budget, 1964-1965 (Box 1, Folder 8)
    - Budget, 1965-1966 (Box 1, Folder 9)
    - Chronological, July 1, 1965 - June 30, 1966 (Box 1, Folder 10-12)
    - Chronological, July 1, 1966 - June 30, 1967 (Box 1, Folder 13-16)
    - Centennial Planning Committee, 1960 (Box 1, Folder 17)
    - Committees, 1965-1967 (Box 1, Folder 18)
    - Ad Hoc Committee - Select Dean of Graduate School, 1964 (Box 1, Folder 19)
    - Economic Status of the Faculty, 1962-1965 (Box 1, Folder 20)
    - Economic Status of the Faculty - Student Exchange (Box 1, Folder 21)
    - Environmental Health, 1965-1966 (Box 1, Folder 22)
    - Extra Mural and Summer Session, 1960-1965 (Box 1, Folder 23)